[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
Oh, fuck. Fuck!
♪ ♪
Are you sure it's him?
I saw him hit the pavement.
Maruyama-san,
before Nakahara fell,
I saw Tozawa enter
the building.
Do you have photos of that?
No. But he was there.
Fine.
We'll include that detail.
Start dictating.
[both speaking Japanese]
Answer me.
What were you looking for
in my study?
Nothing.
I was curious to see
where you live, where you work.
Don't lie to me.
I'm not lying to you.
I'm not a stupid man.
I'm not--
come on, I was just--
oh, okay.
What the fuck?
What's on this?
Did you photograph
my blueprints?
[sighs] I don't understand.
What use is my work to you?
[soft dramatic music]
My club is half-owned
by the Yakuza.
They found out
about your project.
They asked me
to get the information.
I said I would if they give me
the club, free and clear.
So you did it for yourself.
Yes.
And for the girls, too,
to protect them.
I see.
For the girls.
And my career gets ruined
in the process.
You can sleep on the couch.
It's too late
to drive you home.
We'll discuss this tomorrow.
♪ ♪
[sirens wailing]
[indistinct chatter]
[speaking Japanese]
[speaking Japanese
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[breathing heavily]
[both speaking Japanese
[neck cracks]
[engine whirring]
Oi! Oi! Oi!
[speaking Japanese]
[baby crying]
♪ ♪
Come with me.
Masa-san, I am so sorry.
I won't tell them what I saw.
I'll say you caught me first,
that I couldn't find anything.
Ishida will have
to accept that.
And what if
you do not provide Ishida
with the location?
What will he do to you?
That's not your problem.
I got myself into this mess.
I'll get myself out.
There's another project
I'm working on,
early stages.
If Ishida bought surrounding
properties there instead,
he could make
a significant return.
But you'd still be ruined.
Maybe not.
Unlike Shimbashi,
this one is a private venture.
If there was a run
on nearby real estate,
the owners would profit
and likely ask no questions.
If we convinced Ishida
to accept this,
you could keep your club,
and I could keep my job.
What if I could get
someone I know
to publish the location
of your project in the press?
Wouldn't that make
the Shimbashi information
worthless?
And then I could make
my proposal
of a valuable replacement.
Why are you helping me?
I know what it is
to need forgiveness.
Thank you
for the call last night.
It was smart of you
not to talk to anyone else.
Of course.
You know there's no way
that Nakahara jumped, right?
I just wish
I would have gotten a picture
of Tozawa
entering the building.
That fucker never
came back out.
I will get back to you
with anything we learn.
And by we,
you mean that female detective
who sent me packing
the other day?
How's that working out?
She's, like, your new partner
or something?
It is working fine.
Great.
But we're still a thing, right?
Starsky and Hutch?
Which of us is Starsky?
Me, obviously.
I do not think so.
[both speaking Japanese]
[silverware clatters]
[smacks table]
♪ ♪
- [whispering indistinctly]
- Ah.
[whispering indistinctly]
[speaking Japanese
all: Hai.
[phone buzzing]
[speaking Japanese
[door slams]
[indistinct chatter]
[both speaking Japanese
And it's for sure that
this complex is being built
over Shimbashi Station?
Yep, I've seen
the blueprints.
It won't be announced
for a good year,
but that's where it's going.
This anything to do
with Ishida?
Can you just do this for me?
Are you in trouble?
Fine.
I'll follow it up.
[glass shatters]
[speaking Japanese
What's up with you?
There's something
I need to tell you.
Tozawa's back in Tokyo.
I saw him
at his lawyer's office,
and I followed him to a medical
building in Minato-ku.
I'm gonna make him pay
for what he did.
I'm not giving up.
Jake, I love you
for wanting to take him on,
but having a death wish
isn't sexy.
We had videotape
of his men killing Pol--
no consequences.
His men beat you up--
So no, I'd rather not
find out one day
that you just disappeared,
and there will be
no consequences.
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[sighs]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese
[chuckles]
[both laugh]
They know the actual location
of where the project is
being built?
Yeah, my source
just called me.
They said Shimbashi.
Are they in
the transport office?
No, they're...
in a different field,
but I trust them.
Maruyama-san?
Have the article ready
for tomorrow's edition.
I was thinking...
Kurihira should do it.
You want to give away
your scoop?
I think
he could really use it.
You know, Baku's been
riding him really hard.
Fine.
Oh, and your request for your
trip to America was approved.
Oh.
Oh, I'm just not sure,
what with everything going on,
that I should go, you know...
Jake, there will
always be stories,
but you have only one family.
The Ministry will say
no comment,
so you'll just need
to bluff a little.
I see.
Make them think
that you already have
proof of the location.
You just need confirmation.
But don't say the name.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Jake-san,
thank you for this tip.
We gotta look out
for each other, right?
You got this.
♪ ♪
[bright music playing]
[singing in Japanese]
Ah?
[laughs]
Oi.
[music stops]
[baby crying]
[speaking Japanese]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[door slams]
[lock clicks]
[both speaking Japanese]
[sighs]
♪ ♪
- Are you serious?
- Huh?
We are taking them out.
[clears throat]
It was temporary.
It doesn't matter.
It isn't really my club,
as you made perfectly clear.
No, no,
it's actually two circles
going in opposite directions.
So let me get this straight.
You're talking about
the Yamanote Line
that makes the big circle
around Tokyo.
Yes.
The outer track runs clockwise,
the inner track
counterclockwise.
So if you prefer foreign men,
we say you ride
the outer track.
So I'm a foreign man.
Well...
[both laugh]
And if you stick
to native Japanese men,
you ride the inner track, right?
[both speaking Japanese]
So I guess
you're a outer track man, huh?
Actually,
tonight was my first time
on that track.
Really?
Thank you.
What about you?
To be honest,
it's been a year
since I've been with anyone.
Really?
Why?
I got tired of not liking
the people in my bed.
Thank you.
It was a big deal for me
to approach you at that party.
I haven't done that
in a long time.
You have a lot of lost time
to make up for.
If you can keep up.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[both moaning]
[both breathing heavily]
[laughs]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[lock rattling]
[lock clicks]
♪ ♪
So here's
Tozawa's file, right?
And here are the files
of four other Yaks.
Are you sure they're Yakuza?
Dude, you know
how many fanzines I read.
I know all their names.
Illness of the trade.
We call it shokugoyo.
Yakuza live a life
filled with alcohol,
shabu, and tattoo needles.
Do that long enough
and you get liver disease.
Well, it seems
Tozawa has it--
or did.
It's not something
they get over.
[speaking Japanese]
[speaking Japanese
Hayama.
Sato.
Hai.
♪ ♪
Iya.
[both speaking Japanese
[watch beeps]
[line beeps]
[suspenseful music]
[train horn blares]
♪ ♪
[pop music playing]
[speaking Japanese]
Hai.
Hey!
You want to hit one?
No.
I have a busy night, Meicho.
What's so important?
I got you something.
To thank you for taking care
of that kid in jail.
Oh.
Just one?
One more favor,
and then I give you the other.
Huh.
Oyabuns just give up and die?
I don't believe it.
Some try to fight it
and go to Thailand.
There is a German doctor there.
For... about six months?
Then they die.
Ta-da!
Yeah, not bad.
These are too small.
Hey, wait you got
a little brother, right?
Give 'em to him.
Okay.
- Hey, you want to hit one?
- No, no, no.
Come on, five minutes.
You should practice more.
Thank you.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
Aa.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- Right?
It's like this rose--
I think it's rose.
I don't know. I have no idea.
You can use it.
Ladies, listen up.
We have a big night tonight.
Important guest.
Is it Liam Gallagher?
[laughter]
It's not Liam Gallagher,
but I do need you all
in top form.
[speaking Japanese]
Okay.
Samantha?
What happened
with your architect?
Oh, it's so complicated.
I think tonight,
everything gets sorted.
No more Chihara-kai.
I'm offering Ishida a deal.
And if he takes it,
the club is mine 100%.
Samantha, be smart.
Yakuza do not give things back.
It won't work!
It has to work.
Okay.
Let me run the floor tonight.
Whatever you need,
I'm there for you.
Thank you.
- Hai.
- Arigato.
Is that how we look out
for each other, Jake-san,
by stabbing me in the back?
What are you talking about?
You gave me shit advice
so I would fail.
Dude, I told you
not to say the actual name.
After you did that,
the Ministry had to announce.
That's on you, Tin-Tin.
[soft pop music]
♪ ♪
[singing in Japanese]
[applause]
[laughter]
[indistinct chatter]
No matter how this goes,
I'd like to take you
to dinner tomorrow.
A real date.
I don't think the mama-san
is supposed to date clients.
Just one client
who I'm very grateful to
and very attracted to.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
[tense music]
[glass clinking]
[all muttering]
[laughter]
[applause]
♪ ♪
[all cheering]
Banzai!
all: Banzai!
[applause]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Yeah, yeah.
[pop music playing]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
Oi.
[speaking Japanese]
[elevator dings]
♪ ♪
[gunshots]
[all screaming]
♪ ♪
[gun clicks]
[groans]
[gunshots]
[gun clicking]
♪ ♪
[groaning]
[somber music]
♪ ♪